Thanks, Dan. As mentioned earlier, we'll be using Android Studio throughout this
course. It's an IntelliJ -based IDE that is optimized specifically for
Android development. It's still in beta development, so
your version may look slightly different, but that's okay.
The core functionality should still be the same. If you haven't installed it
yet, take a moment to do that now using the detailed instructions provided in
the link below. You'll also need to install the support library and that's also
included in the instructions. Note that the SDK is included automatically, so
you don't need to install that separately. If you're having difficulties, no
worries at all. We totally understand because it can be tricky to get everything
set up properly. You can search online for people who have a similar issue or
there's a troubleshooting link included below. If you still need help, you can
ask a question in our discussion forum as well. Once you install it, open it and
you can check for updates before proceeding. Check this box when you're done.